Guide to the Doris Duke Photograph Collection, 1870-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Duke Farms, 1897-2004
  - Photographs of household items at Duke Farms (includes images of coffee table and Asian figures and boxes), 1982 and undated (Box 24, Folder PHDF335)
  - Photographs of the library and the Victorian (Yellow) Bedroom at Duke Farms, circa 1983 (Box 24, Folder PHDF336)
  - Color slides of Duke Farms, 1986 Dec (Box 24, Folder PHDF337)
  - Black and white photographs of the statuary in the ruin of the old barn, taken by John L Sharpe and sent to Miss Duke, 1988 Mar (Box 24, Folder PHDF338)
  - Photographs, Duke Farms and Gardens, 1988 (Box 24, Folder PHDF339)
  - Color photographs of various barns, houses, and animals at Duke Farms, 1997 (Box 24, Folder PHDF340)
  - Black and white photographs of various Duke Farms scenes, including statuary, Farm Barn and Pump House, undated (Box 24, Folder PHDF341)
  - Photograph, aerial picture of Duke Farms property, 2578-4, undated (Box 24, Folder PHDF342)
  - Photographs of furniture inventoried at Duke Farms (includes photographs of chairs and tables), undated (Box 24, Folder PHDF343)
  - Coach Barn [?] at Duke Farms, circa late 1800s (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder PHDF348)
  - Coach Barn [?] at Duke Farms, circa late 1800s (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder PHDF349)
  - Coach Barn at Duke Farms, 1897 (Box 25, Folder PHDF350)
  - Cow Pasture at Duke Farms, circa 1900s (Box 25, Folder PHDF351)
  - Tinted photographs of various Duke Farms scenes, circa 1900s (1 of 3) (Box 26, Folder PHDF344)
  - Tinted photographs of various Duke Farms scenes, circa 1900s (2 of 3) (Box 26, Folder PHDF344)
  - Tinted photographs of various Duke Farms scenes, circa 1900s (3 of 3) (Box 27, Folder PHDF344)
  - Black and white photographs of Duke Farms and Jersey cattle, 1940s and undated (Box 27, Folder PHDF347)
  - Barn at Duke Farms [?], circa late 1800s (Box 28, Folder PHDF352)
  - Duke Farms Coach Barn, circa late 1800s (Box 28, Folder PHDF353)
  - Aerial photo of Farm Barn and Surrounding Buildings, undated (Box 28, Folder PHDF354)
  - Photograph of Main Residence, undated (Box 28, Folder PHDF355)
  - Unknown Farm, undated (Box 28, Folder PHDF356)
  - Unknown Farm, Orange County, NC [?], undated (Box 28, Folder PHDF357)
  - Unknown House, undated (Box 28, Folder PHDF358)
  - Duke Farms Historic Photographs - Garden and Residence Interiors, circa 1900s (Box 29, Folder PHDF359)
  - Duke Farms Historic Photographs - Fountains, circa 1900s (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder PHDF360)
  - Duke Farms Historic Photographs - Fountains, circa 1900s (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder PHDF360)
  - Duke Farms Historic Photographs - Statues, circa 1900s (Box 29, Folder PHDF361)
  - Duke Farms Historic Photographs - Other Structures, circa 1900s (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder PHDF362)
  - Duke Farms Historic Photographs - Other Structures, circa 1900s (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder PHDF362)
  - Duke Farms Historic Photographs - Lakes, circa 1900s (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder PHDF363)
  - Duke Farms Historic Photographs - Lakes, circa 1900s (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder PHDF363)
  - Duke Farms Historic Photographs - General Views, circa 1900s (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder PHDF364)
  - Duke Farms Historic Photographs - General Views, circa 1900s (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder PHDF364)
  - Sepia photographs of Duke Farms operations, circa late 1800s-early 1900s (1 of 4) (Box 74, Folder PHDF365)
  - Sepia photographs of Duke Farms operations, circa late 1800s-early 1900s (2 of 4) (Box 74, Folder PHDF365)
  - Sepia photographs of Duke Farms operations, circa late 1800s-early 1900s (3 of 4) (Box 74, Folder PHDF365)
  - Sepia photographs of Duke Farms operations, circa late 1800s-early 1900s (4 of 4) (Box 74, Folder PHDF365)
- Duke Gardens, 1958-2000
  The photographs and slides in this series document the history of the gardens from its inception to its dissolution. Subjects include the construction phases of transforming the greenhouses to display gardens, repair work to the display gardens, interior shots of the various display gardens (including flowers, statues, fountains, etc.), and a fashion photo shoot in Duke Gardens in 1964. Of particular interest are the color slides and View-Master "reels" of Duke Gardens that were available for purchase.
  - Selection of slides documenting construction of the Duke Gardens, 1960-1963 (Box 31, Folder PHDG001)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs of the interior gardens of the greenhouse. Photos mostly stamped, "Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc.", 1970-1975 (Box 31, Folder PHDG002)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs of the interior gardens of the greenhouse, 1970-1975 (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder PHDG003)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs of the interior gardens of the greenhouse, 1970-1975 (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder PHDG003)
  - Black and white photographs of the Indo-Persian garden under construction, 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder PHDG004)
  - Sampling of souvenir slides of the gardens that were on sale at the Visitors Center to guests at Duke Farms, 1970-1975 (Box 31, Folder PHDG005)
  - Series of color photos removed from red and white photo album. Photos show interiors of Gardens and various flowers and statues. One photo shows single geyser-like fountain outside, 1967-1970 (Box 31, Folder PHDG006)
  - Color slides of display gardens, circa 2000 (Box 31, Folder PHDG007)
  - Selection of color photos of the Gardens, 1981 (Box 31, Folder PHDG008)
  - Color and Black and white photographs documenting construction phases of the display gardens, circa 1958 (Box 31, Folder PHDG009)
  - Black and white reproduction of the exterior of the display gardens, undated (Box 31, Folder PHDG010)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs documenting the construction phases of transforming the greenhouses into display gardens, 1959 (Box 32, Folder PHDG011)
  - Color Polaroids and 1 Black and white Polaroid of scenes from within the interior display gardens, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder PHDG012)
  - Black and white photographs of interior gardens. Reverse is stamped, "Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc.", undated (Box 32, Folder PHDG016)
  - Black and white photographs of interior gardens. Gardens include French, Chinese, and Indo-Persian, circa 1965 (Box 32, Folder PHDG017)
  - Color slides of repair work within the interior gardens, 1970 (Box 32, Folder PHDG018)
  - Duplicate slides of Duke Gardens that were available for purchase. Includes Desert, English Topiary, Tropical, French, Colonial, Chinese and Japanese Gardens, 1962-1977 (1 of 3) (Box 32, Folder PHDG019)
  - Duplicate slides of Duke Gardens that were available for purchase. Includes Desert, English Topiary, Tropical, French, Colonial, Chinese and Japanese Gardens, 1962-1977 (2 of 3) (Box 32, Folder PHDG019)
  - Duplicate slides of Duke Gardens that were available for purchase. Includes Desert, English Topiary, Tropical, French, Colonial, Chinese and Japanese Gardens, 1962-1977 (3 of 3) (Box 32, Folder PHDG019)
  - Color photograph of the interior of the Japanese Garden. Photo mounted to cardboard backing, circa 1970 (Box 33, Folder PHDG015)
  - Small (2x2) Color Slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1962-1972 (Box 34, Folder PHDG020)
  - Color slides of various gardens at Duke Gardens, taken by Richard C. Page, who was employed by Duke Gardens from 1963 to 1965. Includes individual explanation of each slide, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder PHDG021)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1963 (Box 34, Folder PHDG022)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens taken by R.D. Padgett, Somerville, NJ, 1964 Mar 24 (Box 34, Folder PHDG023)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, 1964 May (Box 34, Folder PHDG024)
  - Color photographs of greenhouses at Duke Gardens, taken by Johnny Gomez, 1964 (Box 34, Folder PHDG025)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1964 (Box 34, Folder PHDG026)
  - Black and white photographs from a fashion photo shoot in Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1964 (Box 34, Folder PHDG027)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ. Includes Tropical, Indo-Persian, Japanese, Chinese, English Topiary, French, English, Desert Gardens, and Foyer, 1964-1969 (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder PHDG028)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ. Includes Tropical, Indo-Persian, Japanese, Chinese, English Topiary, French, English, Desert Gardens, and Foyer, 1964-1969 (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder PHDG028)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ. Includes Italian, Colonial, Edwardian, French Foyer, Knott, English, Chinese, Japanese, Indo-Persian, Tropical, and Semi-Tropical Gardens, 1964-1969 (Box 35, Folder PHDG029)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1965 (1 of 5) (Box 35, Folder PHDG030)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1965 (2 of 5) (Box 35, Folder PHDG030)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1965 (3 of 5) (Box 35, Folder PHDG030)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1965 (4 of 5) (Box 35, Folder PHDG030)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1965 (5 of 5) (Box 35, Folder PHDG030)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, 1965 Aug-Sep (Box 36, Folder PHDG031)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, 1966 Jun (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder PHDG032)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, 1966 Jun (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder PHDG032)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1966 (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder PHDG033)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1966 (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder PHDG033)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1967 (Box 36, Folder PHDG034)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1968 (Box 36, Folder PHDG035)
  - Color photographs of Duke Gardens, 1968 (Box 37, Folder PHDG036)
  - Color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1969 (Box 37, Folder PHDG037)
  - Large color slides of Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1970 (Box 37, Folder PHDG038)
  - Prints and negatives of reconstructions of the Italian Garden, Indo-Persian Garden, and Bonsai project at Duke Gardens, circa 1970s (Box 37, Folder PHDG039)
  - Color photographs of interiors of greenhouses and gardens, 1977 Mar (Box 37, Folder PHDG040)
  - Color photographs of Duke Gardens, 1980 Jan (Box 37, Folder PHDG041)
  - Color photographs of Duke Gardens, 1981 Jan (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder PHDG042)
  - Color photographs of Duke Gardens, 1981 Jan (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder PHDG042)
  - Polaroid photographs of Portico in Italian Garden, Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, 1998 Jan (Box 37, Folder PHDG043)
  - Black and white photographs of Indo-Persian garden reconstruction, undated (Box 37, Folder PHDG044)
  - Photographs, negatives, color slides, and View-Master depicting Gardens. Includes aerial views of garden exterior, undated (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder PHDG045)
  - Photographs, negatives, color slides, and View-Master depicting Gardens. Includes aerial views of garden exterior, undated (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder PHDG045)
  - Small and large color slides of Old Westbury Gardens, undated (Box 38, Folder PHDG046)
  - Black and white photograph of bridge at Duke Gardens, Somerville, NJ, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 38, Folder PHDG051)
  - Duke Gardens slides that have been in publications, undated (Box 38, Folder PHDG052)
  - Black and white interior shot of Duke Gardens, circa 1960s-1970s (1 of 4) (Box 39, Folder PHDG047)
  - Black and white interior shot of Duke Gardens, circa 1960s-1970s (2 of 4) (Box 39, Folder PHDG047)
  - Black and white interior shot of Duke Gardens, circa 1960s-1970s (3 of 4) (Box 39, Folder PHDG047)
  - Black and white interior shot of Duke Gardens, circa 1960s-1970s (4 of 4) (Box 39, Folder PHDG047)
  - Four color photographs of interiors of Duke Gardens, circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder PHDG048)
  - Black and white matted photograph of French Garden at Duke Gardens, undated (Box 40, Folder PHDG049)
  - Aerial photograph of greenhouses at Duke Gardens, undated (Box 40, Folder PHDG050)
- Duke Family, 1870-2006
  The series primarily consists of photographs of various immediate Duke family members including James Buchanan (J.B.) and Nanaline Duke and Ben and Sarah Duke. Of particular interest are the black and white photographs and negatives of J.B. Duke's tour of Lake St. John and the Saguenay from Roberval in 1915.
  - Black and white portrait of James B. Duke (seated) with brother, Benjamin N. Duke, 1910-1920 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM001)
  - Black and white reproduction of photograph of James B. Duke's car with chauffeur, 1915-1920 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM002)
  - Black and white photographs of James B. Duke and Benjamin N. Duke, walking and riding on the Boardwalk, possibly in Atlantic City, NJ, 1920-1925 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM003)
  - Black and white photograph of Ben Duke and Sarah Pearson Angier, walking on the Boardwalk at Atlantic City, NJ, 1920-1925 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM005)
  - Family portrait of Mary Duke Biddle Semans and James Hustead Seamans, MD with her children aboard the Saxonia for a summer trip to Europe. Includes note to Aunt Nanaline and baby picture, most likely of Mrs. Seman's youngest, 1960-1970 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM006)
  - Black and white portrait of Nanaline Duke, standing, with chauffeur and car in the background, 1950-1955 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM007)
  - Portrait of James B. Duke. Portrait is taken of Mr. Duke's left profile, 1900-1910 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM008)
  - Black and white portrait of Nanaline Duke, undated (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM009)
  - Oval, Black and white portrait of Nanaline Duke. Nanaline Duke is wearing a string of pearls and a beaded, lace top, 1915 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM010)
  - Series of Black and white photographs documenting James B. Duke's tour of Lake St. John and Saguenay from Roberval, 1915 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM023)
  - Reproduction of Black and white photograph of Washington Duke standing outside his first factory, the original tobacco barn, circa 1880 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM024)
  - Black and white photographs of Lillian McCredy Duke, James B. Duke's first wife, 1900-1905 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM025)
  - Portraits of James B. Duke, 1900-1910 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM026)
  - Black and white photographs and color photographs of Lynnwood or White Oaks, the former James B. Duke home in Charlotte, NC, 1976 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM027)
  - Black and white photographs of unidentified home, possibly Greenfield Plantation, Walker Inman Sr.'s home. Miss Duke can be seen on the front steps of home, circa 1940 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM028)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs removed from binder. Photos include menu and seating chart from dinner event, 1902-1903 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM029)
  - Reproductions of Black and white photographs of "Doris" Pullman car at its dedication at Duke University. Car was restored thanks to Duke and other donors, 1992 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM030)
  - Black and white photograph of James B. Duke and Benjamin Duke, 1920-1925 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM031)
  - Black and white photograph of James B. Duke with unidentified young woman. Location unknown, possibly Myers Park, NC, 1920-1925 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM032)
  - Black and white photograph of a group of officers and directors of the Southern Power Company at the completion of the Great Falls Station, Catawba River, S.C. James B. Duke is standing to the right of the sign. (L to R): W.S. Lee, B.N. Duke, Dr. Wylie, JB Duke, Mary Duke Biddle, 1905 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM033)
  - Color transparencies and digital images of family portraits, including J.B. Duke, Washington Duke, Artelia Roney Duke, and Nanaline Holt Inman Duke, 2006 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM034)
  - Color photographs of James B. Duke statue at Duke Chapel, Duke University. James B. Duke, with his father and brother, is interred at the Memorial Chapel, 1971 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM035)
  - Tinted portrait of a young James Buchanan Duke, circa 1870s (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM040)
  - Miscellaneous portrait and negatives of J.B. Duke, including J.B. at Duke Farms, circa 1900s and undated (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM041)
  - Portrait of James B. Duke, circa 1914 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM042)
  - Prints and negatives of James B. Duke at the Saguenay River, Canada, 1915 (Box 41, Folder PHDKFM043)
  - Duke Homestead, Orange County, NC, circa 1900s (Box 42, Folder PHDKFM011)
  - Photographs of James B. Duke's funeral in Durham, NC. Photographs are from album with Mrs. J.B. Duke inscribed on the front cover, 1925 (Box 42, Folder PHDKFM014)
  - Portrait of James B. Duke, circa 1924 (Box 42, Folder PHDKFM016)
  - Oval Portrait of Nanaline Duke, 1890-1900 (Box 42, Folder PHDKFM018)
  - Oval portrait of Nanaline Duke. Handwritten on bottom of portrait, "Nanaline Inman (Mrs. Jas B. Duke)", 1890-1900 (Box 42, Folder PHDKFM019)
  - Two portraits of Nanaline Duke, wearing a pearl necklace and pearl earrings. Photographer Mishkin Studio, NYC, 1910-1915 (Box 42, Folder PHDKFM020)
  - Black and white mounted photographs of Benjamin Duke's farm in Orange County, NC, circa 1900s (Box 42, Folder PHDKFM039)
  - Reproduction of Doris Duke posing with James B. Duke (PHDKFM012), 1919 (Box 42, Folder PHDKFM054)
  - Black and white photograph of young Doris Duke sitting on James Buchanan Duke's knee, circa 1914 (Box 43, Folder PHDKFM012)
  - Black and white photographs of house and farm where James B., Benjamin, and Mary Duke were born. Included in file is photo of Duke Factory. Washington Duke can be seen sitting on front porch of house, 1900-1901 (Box 43, Folder PHDKFM013)
  - Portrait of Nanaline Duke, 1900-1910 (Box 43, Folder PHDKFM015)
  - Portrait of Nanaline Duke holding baby Doris. Handwritten note on portrait, "Nanaline Duke and Baby Doris six months, 1913 Jun (Box 43, Folder PHDKFM017)
  - Portrait of Nanaline Duke. Mrs. Duke is leaning against an ornate structure. She also is wearing an elegant dress and wrap, 1910 (Box 43, Folder PHDKFM022)
  - Oversize portrait of James B. Duke, 1900-1910 (Box 43, Folder PHDKFM026)
  - Oversize Black and white portrait of Nanaline Duke. Nanaline Duke is wearing a string of pearls and a beaded, lace top, 1916 (Box 44, Folder PHDKFM010)
  - Portrait of Nanaline Duke, dressed in long elegant dress and wide brim hat. Three copies, circa 1910 (Box 44, Folder PHDKFM021)
  - Photograph of J.B. Duke and unknown group, undated (Box 44, Folder PHDKFM036)
  - Photograph of Duke family, including James B., Benjamin, and Washington. Others in photograph unknown, circa 1900s (Box 44, Folder PHDKFM037)
  - Portrait of Lillian McCredy Duke, undated (Box 44, Folder PHDKFM038)
  - Five photographs of Duke Homestead. Washington Duke is seen in one of the photos, circa late 1800s-early 1900s (Box 45, Folder PHDKFM049)
  - Washington Duke, J.B. Duke, Ben Duke, Brodie Duke[?], and other men in boats on river, undated (Box 45, Folder PHDKFM050)
  - Washington Duke[?], J.B. Duke[?] at Duke Farms, undated (Box 45, Folder PHDKFM051)
  - Hosts & Guests at a banquet tendered for HRH Prince Henry of Prussia, New York. J.B. Duke was in attendance, 1902 Feb 26 (reprinted 1905) (Opaperfolder PHDKFM052)
  - James Cromwell, reprinted from Men's Wear, circa 1930s-1940s (Opaperfolder PHDKFM053)
- Falcon Lair, 1953-1998
  The images in this series are primarily interior and exterior shots of Falcon Lair dating from the time of its purchase by Doris Duke to the time of its sale and the moving out of its belongings.
  - Falcon Lair aerial photograph, 1962 (Box 33, Folder PHFL012)
  - Color photos of exterior views of Falcon Lair and surrounding area. Photos show two members of housekeeping staff, German Shepherd, and cat, 1956 (Box 46, Folder PHFL001)
  - Black and white photograph of crystal chandelier hung at Falcon Lair. Handwritten note on back reads, "Price for chandelier $1500", 1956 Jan (Box 46, Folder PHFL002)
  - Series of color photos portraying the interior rooms at Falcon Lair. Photos include interiors of Music Room (2nd Fl), Napoleon Room (1st Fl), Living Room (2nd Fl), DD's fireplace in Master Bedroom (1st Fl), and upstairs hall. Johnny Gomez appears in 2 of the photographs, 1953-1960 (Box 46, Folder PHFL003)
  - Selection of slides relating to Falcon Lair. Most photos focus on the exterior of the residence and foliage. File includes 2 photos of unidentified boy (possibly Walker Inman Jr), 1960-1970 (Box 46, Folder PHFL004)
  - Color photos of swan bed, most likely in Living Room, and one shot of exterior of Falcon Lair, undated (Box 46, Folder PHFL005)
  - Selection of slides documenting people and dogs at Falcon Lair. Includes Joey Castro, 1959 Jan (Box 46, Folder PHFL006)
  - Black and white photographs of the exterior of Falcon Lair, circa 1953 (Box 46, Folder PHFL007)
  - Color photographs of objects and interior shots of Falcon Lair at time of sale and of moving out, 1998 (Box 46, Folder PHFL008)
  - Color polaroids documenting damage to the interior and exterior of Falcon Lair, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder PHFL009)
  - Black and white photographs of Falcon Lair, prior to Doris Duke's purchase, circa 1925-1926 (reprinted in 1985) (Box 46, Folder PHFL010)
  - Color photographs of Falcon Lair, circa 1988 (Box 46, Folder PHFL011)
- General, 1909-2001 and undated
  The general series is the largest of the series and includes all images that do not logically fit into the other series. The subjects of the images vary widely and include photographs of intimates, friends, and acquaintances of Doris Duke, portraits of unknown men and women, dogs at various estates, unknown buildings and gardens, inventories of furniture and art objects, and reproductions of photographs mounted on foam core that were used for various exhibits. Of particular interest are the black and white stereoscopic image manufactured by the Keystone Stereoscopic Service. These were most likely used by Doris Duke to help strengthen her vision.
  - A Portrait of Nanaline Duke by John C. Hughes, South Kensington, undated (reproduction on foam core) (Box 33, Folder PHGEN104)
  - Print of Chapel, Duke University, undated (Box 33, Folder PHGEN105)
  - Sepia photographs of Franco Rossellini inscribed to Doris Duke, undated (Box 33, Folder PHGEN106)
  - Slides of paintings from a lab in Los Angeles, California, undated (Box 33, Folder PHGEN107)
  - Studio portraits of unknown people, probably Doris Duke's acquaintances, undated (Box 33, Folder PHGEN108)
  - Color portraits of Porfirio Rubirosa, alone, and with unidentified man. In photo with man, "Rubi" is dressed in his polo attire, 1947-1948 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN001)
  - Black and white photographs of Porfirio Rubirosa, standing with fellow polo players and on horse, 1947-1948 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN002)
  - Black and white portraits of actor Rudolph Valentino. Three of these portraits are personally signed by Valentino. Two portraits are duplicates, 1915-1925 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN003)
  - Black and white portrait of Ben [Giles] dressed in military attire. Inscription reads, "To Doris MY OSS friend Ben Giles Cairo 1944", 1944 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN009)
  - Selection of color photos of Porfirio Rubirosa, possibly in the Dominican Republic, 1940-1945 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN010)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs of Porfirio Rubirosa with another couple. Some photos show "Rubi" checking under a car, 1940-1945 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN011)
  - Color photos of Porfirio Rubirosa, color and Black and white. Includes two color slides, 1940-1945 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN012)
  - Selection of color photos of Porfirio Rubirosa with other people. Some photos were most likely taken in Hawaii, 1940-1945 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN013)
  - Black and white portraits of Joey Castro. Portraits include headshots in connection with Clover Records, some negatives and contact sheets, 1965 (1 of 3) (Box 47, Folder PHGEN014)
  - Black and white portraits of Joey Castro. Portraits include headshots in connection with Clover Records, some negatives and contact sheets, 1965 (2 of 3) (Box 47, Folder PHGEN014)